vjloops.com 2018-12-31

# VJ Loops- Royalty Free Stock Footage, Media and Visuals

**Welcome to VJLoops.com "A royalty free stock footage, visuals and digital media marketplace"**

**Changes to This Policy**

We may update this Policy from time to time. If we do, we’ll let you know about any material changes, either by notifying you on the Site or by sending you an email. New versions of this Policy will never apply retroactively — we’ll tell you the exact date they go into effect. If you keep using VJLoops after a change, that means you accept this Policy.

**Who We Are**

VJLoops, (together with its subsidiaries, affiliates, agents, representatives, consultants, employees, officers, and directors — collectively, “VJLoops,” “we,” or “us”) provides services that help people bring mixed multimedia creative projects to life. Our main service is a stock media platform for creative editing projects, live performances like concerts, festivals and events that require digital media. We are a DBA based in Lockport, NY.

**How This Policy Applies**

This Policy describes the information we collect from you, how we use that information and our legal basis for doing so. It also covers whether and how that information may be shared and your rights and choices regarding the information you provide to us. If you see a capitalized word, it’s defined in our [Terms of Use](https://www.vjloops.com/pages/terms-and-conditions.html). We use cookies and similar technologies, as described in our [Cookie Policy](https://www.vjloops.com/pages/cookies-policy.html).

By using the Services offered by VJLoops, you’re acknowledging you have agreed to our Terms of Use and that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and our Cookie Policy.

**What We Collect and Receive**

In order for you to create an account on VJLoops and use our Services, we need to collect and process certain information. Depending on your use of the Services, that may include:

  * Information you provide by completing forms on VJLoops — your name, email and postal addresses, telephone number, country of residence, login, and password details. We may ask for this information if you register as a user of the Services, subscribe to our newsletters, upload or submit content through VJLoops, or if you contact us;
  * Information you provide for identity verification purposes when launching a project, including your legal name, business name and Tax ID for business entities, and date of birth. In some cases, our payment processor will request that you provide a secure upload of an identity document (such as your passport, driver’s license or other government-issued ID) to VJLoops;
  * Details of any requests or transactions you make through the Services. VJLoops partners with other companies (such as Stripe) for payment processing, and the payment information you submit is collected and used by them in accordance with their privacy policies (for Stripe’s, click [here](https://stripe.com/us/legal)). VJLoops doesn’t store your payment information apart from the last four digits of your credit card or bank account (as applicable), expiration date, and country, which we require for tax, government regulatory, and security purposes;
  * Information about your activity on and interaction with VJLoops, including use of our mobile apps (such as your IP address, the type of device or browser you use, and your actions on the Site);
  * Information about the ways people visit and interact with our Site, in the form of traffic analytics. You can opt out of being included in Google Analytics [here](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). For more information about our use of data analytics to protect and improve our Services, see our [Cookie Policy](https://www.vjloops.com/pages/cookies-policy.html);
  * Communications you send to us (for example, when you ask for support, send us questions or comments, or report a problem);
  * Information that you submit on or to VJLoops in the form of comments, contributions to discussions, or messages to other users; and
  * The email address associated with your Facebook account, if you choose to sign up using your Facebook credentials. VJLoops will also request permission to access your name, profile picture, and friend list (these permissions are governed by Facebook’s privacy policies and can be managed through your Facebook privacy settings). We never post anything to your Facebook, Twitter, or other third-party accounts without your permission.

You may decline to provide us with your information. However, this will limit your ability to register for an account or use our Services. For example: Downloading free content requires you to sign up as a buyer.  Submitting content for sale requires you to sign up as a contributor. You may review, change or remove your information through your [account settings](https://www.vjloops.com/members/profile_about.php).

**How We Use This Information**

We use the information we collect for the following purposes:

  * To keep your account secure and protect our Services (including to verify the identities of creators and prevent fraud and abuse);
  * To enable us to provide you with our Services, and to improve and promote our Services;
  * To create and administer your account, contact you, and customize your experience on VJLoops (for example, to show you content that we think may interest you based on your previous use); and
  * To track and analyze use of the Services so that we can improve how VJLoops is performing and provide users with the best experience possible.

**European Union Users**

Data protection law in Europe requires a “lawful basis” for collecting and retaining personal information from citizens or residents of the European Economic Area. Our lawful bases include:

  * Performing the contract we have with you: In certain circumstances, we need your personal data to comply with our contractual obligation to deliver the Services, enable creators to establish and display their content (media files), and enable customers to find and make purchases to them.
  * Legal compliance: Sometimes the law says we need to collect and use your data. For example, tax laws require us to retain records of purchases and payments made through our Services.
  * Legitimate interests: This is a technical term in data protection law which essentially means we have a good and fair reason to use your data and we do so in ways which do not hurt your interests and rights. We sometimes require your data to pursue our legitimate interests in a way that might reasonably be expected as part of running our business and that does not materially impact your rights, freedom or interests. 

For example, we use identity, device, and location information to prevent fraud and abuse and to keep the Services secure. We may also send you promotional communications about our Services, subject to your right to control whether we do so. 

We analyze how users interact with our Site so we can understand better what elements of the design are working well and which are not working so well. This allows us to improve and develop the quality of the online experience we offer all our users. 

**How This Information Is Shared**

**Information that’s shared publicly**

When you create an account, we create a basic profile page for you on VJLoops, containing your username, the date the account was created, and a list of content you have purchased or sold depending if you are a buyer or a seller. As a customer your profile is private. Your username appears with the comments you post and messages you send on VJLoops and, if your profile is set to public, people can click your username to view it. If you make your profile public, others will be able to see the following things:

  * The account username you select, and the date the account was created;
  * Any information you choose to add to your profile (like a picture, bio, or your location);
  * Media you’ve uploaded (Contributors Only);
  * Quantity of free and paid downloads (Contributors Only);
  * Comments you’ve posted on VJLoops; and
  * If you have added “friends” on the VJLoops.com (Customers and Contributors).

If you would like to have a public profile, but don’t want others to see your name or profile image on the site, you may choose an account image or name that is not identifiable (e.g., VJ40123). You can modify or delete certain information associated with your account (such as your username, profile image, biography and location) from your [account settings](https://www.vjloops.com/members/profile_about.php), and you can change your privacy settings if you want to make your profile private or adjust the default settings.

Contributors are also asked to verify their identities before submitting content. Once this has been done, the creator’s Verified Name will be publicly displayed on their account profile and on any pages their media is featured.

**Information that isn’t shared publicly**

The following data will not be publicly displayed or revealed to other users:

  * Any payment information you provide;
  * Your password details;
  * Your IP address;
  * Your phone number;
  * Your date of birth and other identity verification documentation (for creators);
  * Private profile information, in accordance with your preferences; and
  * Communications you send to us (for example, when you ask for support, send us questions or comments, or report a problem).

**Information that’s shared with trusted third-party services**

We may share your information with certain trusted third-party services to help us provide, improve, promote, or protect VJLoops’s Services (like when we partner with payment processors, or use services that help us manage our ads on other sites). When we share data with third-party services that support our delivery of the VJLoops Services, we require that they use your information only for the purposes we’ve authorized, and that they protect your personal information at least to the same standards we do. We may also share information that’s aggregated and anonymized in a way that it doesn’t directly identify you.

**Information that’s shared with VJLoops Contributors**

When you purchase content, the contributor will know the amount in dollars you have purchased, the license type, and the resolution you have selected. Contributors never receive personally identifiable information, credit card details or other payment information.

[Contact us ](https://www.vjloops.com/contacts/)if you receive a request for information that seems inappropriate or excessive by anyone claiming to be from VJLoops.com.

**Information that’s shared to protect VJLoops and comply with the law**

We do reserve the right to disclose personal information when we believe that doing so is reasonably necessary to comply with the law or law enforcement, to prevent fraud or abuse, or to protect VJLoops’s legal rights, property, or the safety of VJLoops, its employees, users, or others.  We take copyright and infringement of trademarks very seriously. Contributors agree to upload content that they have created or have the legal right to submit for commercial royalty free use. 

**Links to other websites and services**

Our Site may include links to other websites or services whose privacy practices may differ from VJLoops’s. When you use a link to an external site or service, the privacy policy and data processing disclosures for that site or service governs.

**Retention**

We will retain your information as long as your account is active, as necessary to provide you with the Services or as otherwise set forth in this Policy. We will also retain and use this information as necessary for the purposes set out in this Policy and to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, enforce our agreements and protect VJLoops’s legal rights.

We also collect and maintain aggregated, anonymized or pseudonymized information which we may retain indefinitely to protect the safety and security of our Site, improve our Services or comply with legal obligations.

**Data Transfers**

Because VJLoops is a US-based company, your information will be collected and processed in the United States. The United States has its own laws governing data protection and government access to information. The rules that protect your personal information under United States law may be different than in your home country. If you choose to use the Services, you need to agree to our Terms of Use, which set out the contract between VJLoops and its users.

**Your Rights**

Users residing in certain countries, including the EU, are afforded certain rights regarding their personal information. Except where an exception or exemption applies, these rights include the ability to access, correct, and request deletion of your personal information. While these rights are not applicable globally, all VJLoops users can manage their personal information, as further described below, in their [account settings](https://www.vjloops.com/members/profile_about.php).

You can request a downloadable copy of your personal data from VJLoops from our account settings page. To modify or delete the personal information you’ve provided to us, please log in and update your profile. You may also delete your account by contacting us directly through the verified email on record. We will contact you to verify your account and after you have passed the verification process your account will be deleted. We may retain certain information as required by law or as necessary for our legitimate business purposes.

**Email and Mobile Notifications**

We want to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. We try to keep emails to a minimum and give you the ability to opt in and out to any marketing communications we send.  By signing up to the site you agree to be enrolled in our email marketing campaign.

We will send you email relating to your transactions on VJLoops. You may also elect to receive certain marketing email communications, in accordance with your preferences, and from which you may opt out at any time by adjusting your [notification settings](https://www.vjloops.com/members/profile_about.php). If you download the VJLoops app (in development), you can manage the notifications you receive on your mobile device in your profile settings.

We’ll also send you service-related announcements when it’s necessary to do so.

**Security**

We take security seriously, and the security of your personal data is important to us. We follow industry-standard practices to protect the data we collect and maintain, including using Transport Layer Security (TLS) to encrypt information as it travels over the internet. No method of transmission over the internet or electronic storage is completely secure, so VJLoops cannot guarantee its absolute security. Your account information is protected by a password, which you should choose carefully and keep secure. We encourage all users to enable two-factor authentication (in development) in [account settings](https://www.vjloops.com/members/profile_about.php) to further protect their account.

We have a Security Incident Response Team (SIRT) and protocol in place in the event of a data breach. We encourage the responsible disclosure ofvulnerabilities of our Services by emailing arnas@VJLoops.com, and we will invite valid disclosures to our bug bounty program (in development).

**Data Protection Officer**

To contact our Data Protection Officer, please email Kyle@VJLoops.com.

You can contact us in writing at:

Kyle Lyons

168 Cottage Street 

Lockport, NY 14094

USA

**Data Protection Authority**

Subject to applicable law, if you are a citizen or resident of the European Economic Area, you also have the right to (i) object to VJLoops’s use of your personal information and (ii) lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority or VJLoops’s lead supervisory authority in the European Union.

You can contact us in writing at:

Data Protection Authority

Calle Simon Ortiz #4 pta 3

Valencia 46008

Spain

**Children**

People under 18 (or the legal age in your jurisdiction) are not permitted to use VJLoops on their own. VJLoops does not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 13 and children under 13 are not permitted to register for an account or use our Services.

If you believe that a child has provided us with personal information, please [contact us](https://www.vjloops.com/contacts/). If we become aware that a child under age 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information, we’ll delete it.

_Updated: May 16 th 2018_
